The world is awash in pain.
Now, wars are fought between spies
over information -
in shadow wars.
Time to decide who carries the backpack!
All right!
Most common choice wins!
One, two, shoot!
Damn it, Lily!
You said we'd choose rock together!
Huh? Is that what I said?
You assholes all played me!
I'm sure I have no idea what you're talking about.
I am sorry.
You are the strongest one here, Sis.
The pack's all yours!
I mean, I guess when you put it like that...
Everyone's gotten their jitters out, yeah?
It's time.
Honestly, I'm scared.
I have this bad feeling that just won't go away.
Like we're all making some sort
of horrible misunderstanding.
It's going to be okay, Sara.
You're not alone here.
If something goes wrong,
we'll put our heads together and come up with a plan.
Miss Lily...
All right, Leader, time to go.
Yup!
This battle is going to be Lamplight's big debut.
Is everyone ready to put
their intensive training to the test?
Our infiltration routes will take us in
from the east and the west.
I'll be operating separately from the rest of you.
The sample we're after is somewhere
in this building here,
but we weren't able to track down an exact location.
We'll have to go to the mission site
and get that intel in person.
Abyss Doll...
I can't believe the Empire stole a killer virus.
It spreads via airborne droplets over
its one-week incubation period,
then kills its host within twelve hours
of symptoms appearing.
It's nothing short of evil incarnate.
If they think they can get away with using bioweapons,
they've got another one coming.
There are a number of soldiers and
Imperial spies stationed on-site.
If they find you,
they'll shoot first and ask questions later.
You'll need to deceive everyone
who stands in your way to take them down.
There are three guards.
They're at range fifteen.
Leave it to me, yo!
Oh no, you don't.
Someone was able to escape
Mr. Bernard's surveillance?
That's gotta mean...
...we're dealing with a spy, and a good one.
Let's do this!
Spread out! Quick!
That bomb...
Its explosion was the same color
as the ones my mentor used to use.
Against him, I never once won a fight.
He was always a tenth of a second faster than me,
and I could never close that gap.
After Inferno got wiped out, I ID'd his corpse.
But what if it was a fake?
MISSION: Flower Garden III
That's odd.
My idiot pupil was supposed to be
the one coming in from the west.
Did he change his mind at the last minute?
"Idiot pupil"?
Well, this works.
Once I take all seven of these kids hostage,
that will be that.
It can't be...
You're Teach's mentor, Mr. Guido?
What the hell? You know my name?
That Klaus has got some loose lips.
But how?
Everyone on Inferno is supposed to be dead.
He turned traitor.
He betrayed his team.
I always thought it was weird.
Impossible Mission or not,
it doesn't make sense for a team that legendary
to go down so easily.
But how did you know our infiltration route?
You're not the brightest, are you?
I was on Inferno,
so I used to live in Heat Haze Palace.
I bugged the place to the gills myself.
Is it starting to make sense, little ladies?
We heard everything through the wiretap.
I know everything about you seven,
and I know your entire plan.
If we run, he'll just capture us one by one.
Instead, we should take him on together.
Agreed.
Seven on one, huh?
You're all going down.
Unfortunately for you,
we've got loads of practice fighting while outmatched!
Wires, huh?
What are you...
dumb or something?!
Annette!
Remember where you learned that trap?
The Republic's spy techniques won't work on me.
Six left.
Welcome to hell, kiddos.
Blue Fly has made contact with enemy spies
by the western pipeline block.
Then our information was accurate.
Our counterintelligence department
never fails to impress.
I have a report.
The hostile coming from the east
is heading straight for us here in the main building,
just as we planned.
He might not look it, but he's a total softie.
He's probably freaking out right about now.
He's thinking, "I can't afford to lose another team,"
or something like that.
Now, come on out.
You have ten seconds.
For every second past that, I break one of her fingers.
Buy us some time.
We'll use it to prepare our next move.
You sure made up your mind quickly.
It was the wrong call, though.
You should've abandoned your friend and fled.
We made a decision.
We decided that all seven of us
would make it out alive.
Lamplight wouldn't be Lamplight
without Teach and seven hotties like me.
A rainbow's got seven colors,
and there are seven deadly sins.
It's the perfect number.
We've got me for greed, Thea for lust,
Sybilla for wrath-
Who you callin' "Wrath"?!
She just had throw in that bit
calling herself a hottie, huh?
Having six or eight of us wouldn't feel right.
The seven of us are all going to go back,
together with Teach!
We're ready.
What a headache.
No-
Stay back!
I guess that'd make you "Lust," huh?
If you're trying to bait me, it won't work.
How cold.
Still, you were too slow!
Magnificent.
This is checkmate, Guido!
You seriously thought that disguise would fool me?
He always calls me "Master."
Five left.
Four left.
Thanks, you two.
Now, get him!
What was that, a paralyzing agent?
You must have some sort of poison resistance.
But so what?
We've got this!
Three left.
No way...
My poison didn't work?
Sure it did.
I held my breath as fast as I could,
but it still stings like hell.
See? I can barely feel my fingertips.
Two left.
Run, Miss Lily!
One left.
You son of a...
How dare you hurt my friends?!
Sorry, kid.
All that work you did this past month was for nothing.
Zero left.
A wall?
Too bad, so sad.
All that information you gathered was
bad intel we fed you on purpose.
You must be an Imperial spy.
Blue Fly, or as you knew him, Guido, turned traitor.
And when he did, we got full dossiers
on every spy the Din Republic has.
There's no way in hell you could beat us-
A trap? But when?
I have some questions for you.
And I expect answers.
I figured out what you're after.
It's Teach, right?
He's been your target all along.
Bingo!
Here's the low-down for you.
When we took out Inferno two months ago,
the plan was for him to die, too.
I gave him a special mission to
isolate him from the group.
Him teaming up with the others
would have been a problem.
Back then, I was being sarcastic.
I knew that there was no way he was
making it out of there alive.
But then, imagine my surprise
when the little bastard pulled through.
I sent waves of top-notch Imperial spies after him,
and he put them all in the ground.
As far as the Empire's concerned,
getting rid of him is a top priority.
And so-
You used Abyss Doll as bait to lure him out.
Right again.
Not even he's going to be able to survive this.
When he hears that, he'll come running.
That's how much he cares about his teammates.
Faced with an opponent he can't beat
and the disadvantage of having seven of his students
taken hostage, he'll fight valiantly...
and perish.
You've got it all figured out.
If Teach comes, he'll die,
and if he doesn't, you'll kill us.
Oh no! Whatever will we do?!
I have to ask, Mr. Guido...
How much longer should I keep
playing along with this game?
Can you hear me, Master?
It's been a while.
I just secured the Abyss Doll sample.
The mission is complete.
All that's left for me to do is escape.
MISSION: Flower Garden III
We're about to head to the mission site,
but in all likelihood,  the Empire will be expecting us.
However, that's not a problem.
We'll go in pretending we're none the wiser.
Thinking we know nothing, our enemies will
underestimate us and try to catch me in a trap.
Then, I can turn the tables on them
and secure the intel we need.
So, what's our job?
There's one foe in particular I need you to deceive.
So, we're a diversion, Boss?
Exactly.
By feigning weakness, you can create an opening.
That's your true mission.
Did you hear me, Master?
I'm taking the Abyss Doll sample and going home.
Even if I came over there, I can't beat you in a fight.
It makes more sense for me to prioritize the mission.
Cut the crap!
If you're not here in five minutes-
Oh, and Master,
you're working under a large misconception.
I always suspected that one of Inferno's members
had turned traitor.
I knew it was an inside job since the moment
I heard the news two months ago.
There was no proof.
How could you-
I just did.
If I had to give a reason, though,
it was because I found those bugs
you planted in Heat Haze Palace.
Wait, you found them?!
I did.
That's why the seven girls there and I
operated under the assumption
that a traitor was listening to
everything we did in Heat Haze Palace.
When we first met, I gave them a set
of Communal Living Rules.
For example, one of them was as follows:
Never use your unique talents
inside Heat Haze Palace.
When the girls read the rules,
they understood what I was getting at.
From there, they spent the next month
faithfully obeying them.
In other words, Master, you think you know
what the girls are capable of,
but the truth is, you know nothing.
The dossiers you have on every
full-fledged spy in the Republic
won't do you a bit of good
against the academies' girl wonders.
Each member of Lamplight has
a deadly skill they keep hidden away.
I can say with full confidence that
the girls will defeat you.
I'm code name Flower Garden,
and it's time to bloom out of control.
It smells so acrid...
Is that foam what I think it is?
Yup!
This poison foam takes full advantage
of my abnormal physiology.
I spent this past month coming up with it.
And you don't know a thing about it.
Want to try it on?
You washouts still don't stand a chance against me.
Why even bother getting up?
Because it feels real nice.
You wouldn't get it.
Someone who chose to betray the family
they lived with in Heat Haze Palace never could.
This is for the others, and also...
it's for the ideals Teach is still carrying.
I'm taking you down, Mr. Guido!
Too slow.
It was just for show?
Figures.
Can you hear me, Klaus?
I took out all seven of 'em!
Your students are all-
Was that an accident?
It can't just be a coincidence.
How unlucky...
She was hiding in the white-haired kid's backpack?
It can't be!
Our first coordinated plan,
and I get stuck with the hardest job.
There was an eighth?
Indeed there was.
The eight girls had to live
as if they were seven people.
That was one of the orders I gave them
via the Communal Living Rules.
Allow me to introduce her.
She is...
Lamplight's eighth member.
Fool
I'm Erna.
On the first day,
Lily and the rest of the original seven
were the only ones who arrived.
But on the morning of the second day,
Erna showed up late and
joined the roster as its eighth member.
From that point on, they went about their lives
making sure never to mention
that there were actually eight of them.
It was a trick built around the wiretap.
Seeing them in person would have made it obvious
that there were eight of them,
but it's hard to tell eight girls apart
by their voices alone.
Erna specializes in misfortune,
and she's an expert when it comes to
accidents and disasters.
Her sharp senses let her subconsciously
pick up on portents of doom,
allowing her to get others caught up in them.
There's no way...
Oh, but there is.
She's our super secret ace in the hole.
Yeep.
How many lies did you pile up?
You seriously sacrificed a month of your lives
just to land a single attack?
Just how far did you-
We seriously did.
We're your idiot pupil's pupils, after all.
The plan worked.
Yup!
Now, we can leave the rest to Teach and-
Behind you!
But my stab landed, I know it did!
Yeah, I even passed out for a second.
I gotta hand it to you.
It's been a while since that happened.
My moves are a tenth of a second slower.
That was all your efforts amounted to.
No way! That's it?
That's all we accomplished?
Magnificent.
There you are, Idiot Pupil.
Abyss Doll is in here.
Take it and go.
You got it all on your own?
I couldn't have done it
if you all hadn't distracted my mentor.
I might be a bit.
Go on ahead and take escape route four back to Din.
And like a fountain welling up from a plateau,
remember your training.
That doesn't make sense, but you got it!
That was some excellent work my students did.
Your movements are a tenth of a second slower.
I finally caught up.
Don't get cocky on me, Idiot Pupil.
I'm sorry, Master,
but in your current state,
you aren't qualified to be my enemy.
Impossible Missions have
a ninety percent mortality rate,
but us eight Lamplight girls made it through ours
without losing a single member.
Then, a week later...
Thanks for everything, Teach.
So, the eight of them
all went back to their academies?
That's right.
Lamplight was a provisional team assembled
to complete a single Impossible Mission.
Now that the mission's over,
it makes sense to disband the team.
They won't have to self-deprecatingly
call themselves washouts anymore.
If they can go forward with their heads held high,
then I could ask for nothing more.
You almost sound like a real teacher.
Please.
As an instructor, I was incompetent from start to finish.
Really, now?
I wonder what your mentor
would have to say about that?
What became of Guido's body?
Sadly, this is all I was able to
bring back with me from the Empire.
Why did you betray Inferno, Master?
End it.
Finish the job, Klaus.
I'm not letting you die, not yet.
I'm going to be disbanding Lamplight.
The two of us can rebuild Inferno together, Master.
You can atone for what you did
by putting your life on the line
for the country we all love.
What are you...
You're the only family I have left, Guido.
You're too soft, kid.
Was that a sniper scope just now?
Master!
Make sure you protect 'em this time...
Who was it?
Who took the shot?
We finally caught you!
Wait...
Aren't you supposed to be back at your academies?
We were acting!
Because we're spies, yo!
I'm sorry, Boss.
At long last, our victory is at hand!
Now, we can make whatever demands we want.
What demands?
Do you even have to ask?
We want Lamplight to stay together.
We all talked it over.
And, um, instead of going back to
our academies, graduating,
and getting stuck on teams with a bunch of strangers...
...we figured we would rather stick with the people
we'd already been in the foxhole with.
You could have just asked normally.
Why bother tricking me, locking me up,
and holding me at gunpoint?
We're just continuing your lesson plan.
That class has concluded.
Call it payback, then.
You surrender, right?
We want to keep learning from you.
Teach us how a bunch of former washouts
can come into bloom.
Yeah.
Make sure you protect 'em this time.
I see where you're coming from.
However...
It's as you can see.
You aren't qualified to be my enemies yet.
But that aside...
Magnificent.
Then for all seven of you on Lamplight,
class is back in session.
All eight, I should say.